lehmans.com 2013-04-28

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers the site http://www.lehmans.com which is maintained by Lehman’s Hardware in Dalton Ohio.

Because Lehman’s® would like to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy and the security of the information that you entrust to us, we are disclosing our information practices. Lehman’s® is committed to conforming to the standards of the Better Business Bureau (BBB) and the Direct Marketers Association (DMA)

  * **Information Collected**
    * Order Processing
    * Cookies
    * Log Files

  * **Sharing Information**
    * Framing or Masking
    * Disclosure by Law
    * Policy on Links

  * **Policy Concerning Children**

  * **Information Accuracy**
    * Online Tool
    * Other Tools

  * **Choices and Opt out**
    * Rejecting Cookies
    * Email Opt-out
    * We Can Help

  * **Lehman’s commitment to security**
    * What Lehman’s Does
    * Lehman’s Accountability

  * **Who to Contact at Lehman’s**

Information Collected

Unless otherwise indicated Lehman’s® is the sole owner of any information collected on our web site. Lehman’s® values the relationship we have with our customers and will not sell, share, or rent Personally Identifiable Information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect only pertinent information from our customers to process orders and better serve our customers with necessary information, such as order confirmations and status updates.

Lehman’s® occasionally sends e-mail announcements (for example, announcing upcoming sales or special events). If you do not want to receive such mailings you may opt out of mailings Read More... If you opt-out, Lehman’s® will only use your e-mail address to contact you regarding your order.

Back to top...

Information Collected in Order Processing

Customers of Lehmans.com are presented with a choice of many fine products. You may make a purchase on our online store at any time of the day from any internet-enabled computer from anywhere in the world.

Lehman’s® checkout process involves collecting sensitive information to allow us to ship your purchase to its destination as well as payment information. In the event that there is a problem with your order we may use the information collected to contact you. Lehman’s® will share only necessary information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. Lehman’s will share the information necessary for delivery of your order with the shipping company that delivers it. Currently there are two ways that Lehman’s® customers can check out.

  1. Returning Account Holder
  2. Guest Account

Information collected from Returning Account Holders:

As a returning account holder, you can create an account that will retain your shipping and billing information but not credit card information. Registered users create a user name/password that provides you with access to stored addresses order histories and wish lists. When a new account is created the site will collect the following information:

  * User Name and Password - if you are a registered user of Lehmans.com the site will collect a user name and password you create to access your account information.
  * First Name, Middle Initial ( _optional_ ), and Last Name
  * Optional company information
  * Mailing Address information including Street Address, City, State or Province, Zip or Postal Code, and Country - this is required for billing your credit card.
  * Telephone Number - we ask for a telephone number so we may easily contact you in the event of an order problem.
  * Email Address - Lehmans.com will send you an order confirmation, shipping confirmation and thank you via email.
  * If you require your order to be shipped to a separate address from the billing address the site will collect the additional information to complete your request.
  * The site will also give you an opportunity to sign up for Lehman’s® newsletter and/or sales and specials, and email updates. If you do not wish to be included on the email list leave the appropriate check box unchecked at _Step 1_ of Lehman’s® checkout. If you would like to opt-out of an existing mailing list Click Here for more information.
  * After determining the method you would like to use for shipping your purchase, the site will ask for a payment method. Lehman’s® uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) to encrypt the information transmitted over the internet. Secure Socket Layer (SSL) means that the data transmitted between Lehmans.com and our customer’s browser is encrypted  
In most browsers, a padlock or key icon tells you that you're connected to a secure web site.

Information collected from Guest Accounts:

Lehmans.com offers our customers the option to make a purchase without creating an account. If a customer returns to Lehmans.com to make a purchase they will need to enter the shipping/billing address as well as payment information. Lehman’s® recommends creating an account, which is more convenient for most people.  
The information collected from a guest is the same as the information collected from a registered user with the exception of the user name/password. A guest user will not have access to order histories, stored addresses or wish lists offered to the registered users.

Back to top...

Information Collected via Cookies

Cookies are small packets of information which are stored on the user’s computer. Lehmans.com uses cookies to store selected product information on your hard drive as well as to remember your preferences. When you select a product from our online store the web site will set a cookie on your computer containing a unique ID and information about the order. 

Lehmans.com uses a service to assist our customers as they browse the web site. This service sets a cookie on your computer to help Lehman’s assist you.

Some of Lehman’s® business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access or control over these cookies. This privacy policy only covers cookies set by Lehmans.com

Back to top...

Information Collected via Internet Log files

In order to effectively manage an Online Web Service, it is necessary to get feedback about the activity and performance of the web site as well as any problems that may be occurring. Lehmans.com tracks how our customers use the web site. The information that is collected is not linked to Personally Identifiable Information.

Back to top...

Sharing information

Lehman’s® may use outside companies to provide services for our customers. These services include Live Chat, shipping services for live quotes to our customers, marketing assistance, list servers, data analysis and credit processing. Lehman’s® will provide limited information to these companies and requires that these companies conform to Lehman’s® standards and practices.

Back to top...

Framing or Masking

Lehman’s® may employ third party sites and services that may be framed or masked (placing their web site within a Lehman’s® template to provide the experience of shopping at Lehman’s® web site). If Lehman’s® utilizes this capability, we exercise care in selecting the external web site.

Back to top...

Disclosure by Law

Lehman’s® reserves the right to disclose Personally Identifiable Information as required by law and when we believe disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site.

Back to top...

Policy on Links

Occasionally Lehmans.com will provide links to external web sites that are not covered under this Privacy Policy. Often these links are for the convenience of our guests, and the sites that Lehman’s® will link to contain information we feel is beneficial. However, Lehman’s® cannot control the policies of these sites as they are maintained by external sources, nor can we be responsible for the content of the sites. Lehman’s® encourages guests that navigate to these external sites to consult the Privacy Policy of the site they are visiting for information and practices.

Back to top...

Policy concerning children

Lehmans.com does not sell products for purchase by children. Lehman’s® does sell many products oriented toward children, but these products are for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 18 you may use Lehmans.com only in the presence of a consenting parent or legal guardian. Lehman’s® will not knowingly or intentionally collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 18.

Back to top...

Information Accuracy

Lehmans.com recognizes that information is subject to change. We offer our customers several tools to update the information that Lehman’s® maintains. If you have a registered account on Lehmans.com you may use the online tool any time of day to view and modify the information. You may also inform Lehman’s® of information updates or get help using the tools by email, live chat postal mail, or toll-free telephone. Lehman’s® will gladly perform the updates or provide assistance.

Back to top...

Online Tool

Lehman’s® web site provides registered users of Lehmans.com with a tool to view information that is related to their account including personal information, address books, order information, wish list, and history etc. This tool can be accessed by using the My Account link located on every page of the web site. This tool can only be used by customers that have registered with Lehmans.com.

Back to top...

Other Tools

Lehman’s® is committed to our customers, and we want to hear from you. You may submit information updates or any requests by email [info@lehmans.com](mailto:info@lehmans.com?subject=information%20changes). We provide a tool to [chat with us live](http://server.iad.liveperson.net/hc/1351182/?cmd=file&file=visitorWantsToChat&site=1351182&byhref=1&VISITORVAR!email=privacypolicy) during business hours.   
We can also be contacted by toll free telephone at 1-888-438-5346.  
Customers may also contact us by postal mail at the following address:

Lehman’s®  
289 Kurzen Road North  
Dalton, Ohio 44618

Back to top...

Choice and Opt-Out

Lehman’s® respects the wishes of our customers. If our customers do not wish to be contacted by Lehman’s® we provide several ways to ensure that your information is removed.

Back to top...

Rejecting Cookies

If you wish, you may choose to reject cookies through your browser preferences or internet security software. You may still browse our online store, however, online purchases will not be possible because Lehmans.com shopping cart checkout requires cookies to be enabled. You may telephone an order to our operators by calling 1-888-438-5346.

Back to top...

Email Opt-out

If you do not wish to receive email from Lehman’s® [click here](http://newsletter.lehmans.com/remove.html).  
You may also send us an email specifying that you wish to be removed from email lists at [info@lehmans.com](mailto:info@lehmans.com?subject=Do%20not%20Mail).

Back to top...

We can help

If you make a purchase from Lehman’s®, you may receive mailings from other companies. You may specify that your name and address not be made available to any other company and we will honor your wishes. Email your request to [info@lehmans.com](mailto:info@lehmans.com?subject=Do%20not%20distribute). Please allow 4 - 6 weeks for changes to take effect.  
If you make a purchase from Lehman’s®, you may receive future Lehman’s® Non-Electric catalogs or sale announcements. If you do not want to receive such mailings, please call 1-888-438-5346 or send an e-mail to [info@lehmans.com](mailto:info@lehmans.com?subject=Do%20not%20contact) stating that you do not want mailings from Lehman’s® of any kind.

Back to top...

Lehman’s® commitment to security

Protection of Personally Identifiable Information is very important to the management and staff at Lehman’s®. We take precautions to protect our customers' data. We use proven technology and security, and maintain policies both online and offline to ensure your personal data is protected.

Back to top...

What Lehman’s® does

When a customer is checking out, they are presented with Lehman’s® checkout, a secure environment that utilizes industry leading encryption techniques.

Users can recognize a secure environment by the _padlock_ symbol  and the _https://www.lehmans.com_ in the address bar. Lehman’s® utilizes Verisign® to encrypt the information being passed between the user’s browser and Lehman’s® web server. You may read more about Verisign® by [clicking here...](http://www.verisign.com/) Lehman’s® also provides a link to our encryption information by clicking on the Verisign seal in the footer of the pages or [clicking here...](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&dn=WWW.LEHMANS.COM&lang=en)

Further access to entrusted information is restricted in our physical facilities, since our web server is in a locked, protected environment. 

Back to top...

Lehman’s® Accountability

Lehman’s® continues to evolve as a business, and our Privacy Policy will evolve as well. As technology changes and new methods are introduced, Lehman’s® will continue to employ proven technologies to protect the Personally Identifiable Information our customers entrust to us. As these changes take place the Privacy Policy will change, and the changes will be posted in our statement, our homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that our customers remain aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and how we protect it. Lehman’s® is committed to conforming to the standards of the Better Business Bureau (BBB) and the Direct Marketers Association (DMA).  
Lehman’s® reserves the right to change this policy at any time and without notice, and we encourage our customers to review the policy frequently.

Back to top...

Who to contact at Lehman’s®

All inquiries may be submitted using email, toll free telephone, or postal mail. Please contact us using the following information.

Email | Toll Free Telephone | Postal Mail  
---|---|---  
[info@lehmans.com](mailto:info@lehmans.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) | 1-888-438-5346 | Lehman’s®  
289 Kurzen Road North  
Dalton, Ohio 44618  
  
Back to top...
